Age: 25 Linkedin: http://bit.ly/3GOxYCj

Name: Ernesto Pozzo Email: ernestopablopozzo8@gmail.com

Phone number: 78945126 GitHub: <u>ErnestoPozzo (Ernesto) (github.com)</u>

# **Professional Summary**

I have managed social media pages and structured website updates to gain visibility and establish a community for women entrepreneurs. In addition, I participated in the research and documentation for the writing of papers on the Bolivian Business Ecosystem. I currently work as a business advisor for the board of a hostel in the city of La Paz Bolivia. I have loved technology since I was a child, so I plan to migrate to this industry. For this reason, I learned to code in Kotlin, Python and HTML. I believe my business background allows me to have a unique approach to problem solving.

# **Work Experience**

## Tambo de Oro | 11 2022 - PRESENT

#### Management Adviser

Responsible for sharing insights to management based on financial data and costumer experience.

## Fundación IES | 05/2022 - 11/2022

## Junior Consultant

Helped with research and documentation and with website and social media updates. A scrum methodology was in place for my team, we had weekly sprints and daily zoom meetings.

- Participated in zoom meetings where our goal was to improve and update the foundation's website.
- Created content that was uploaded to social media and the foundation's website.
- Researched and documented data of Bolivian businesses.

## Munay | 12/2021 - 05/2022

#### Operational analyst

Planed and structured internal operations for website inputs and updates. To get my new tasks and update my progress to my team, we used Trello to manage the team with the scrum methodology.

- Built flowcharts for internal operations processes involving the startup's website.
- Involved in meetings regarding the strategic calendar.

## Tambo de Oro | 11/2020 - 12 2020

#### Operational Intern

Assisted with the development of internal operations for customer service.

Helped with the build of flowcharts for internal operations processes for customer service.

#### Marci SRL | 04/2020 - 05/2020

#### Business intern

Gathered data to build a new customer database.

• Mapped new customers based on industrial supplies.

## **Education**

Bachelor par excellence in Business Administration | Universidad Privada Bolviana

# **Technologies I Know**

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Kotlin
- Python
- Git/GitHub/GitLab
- SQL